reelcinemas.ae 2018-12-14

# 

**When you provide us with information through this website, we respect your privacy. It is important for you to understand what we do with information we collect from you through this website. Your visit to this website is subject to this privacy policy.  **

Please direct any questions regarding this Privacy Policy to:    
Reel Cinemas   
P.O. Box 191741   
Dubai, United Arab Emirates 

#### 1\. Information Collection and Use 

When you submit your personally identifiable information, which includes but is not limited to name, nationality, area of residence, contact details and movie preferences, (collectively known as “Personal Information”) on or through this website, please note, you are giving your consent to the following, which includes but is not limited to, the collection, use and disclosure of this Personal Information in the manner as set forth in this Privacy Policy. In the event, you would prefer that we do not collect any Personal Information from you; it is strongly advised that you do not provide us with any such information listed above.

Except as otherwise disclosed in this Privacy Policy, Personal Information provided to us will be used for the purposes, which include but is not limited to processing and sending information and publications, which may contain advertising, promotional or other information relating to or provided by third parties or otherwise for responding to any comments or questions you have or for other internal administrative purposes and to provide in aggregate form for internal business purposes, such as generating statistics and developing marketing plans. We will not sell or rent your Personal Information to third parties without your consent, except as disclosed in this Privacy Policy. We may collect, store or accumulate certain non-Personal Information concerning your use of this website, such as information regarding which of our pages are most popular. This information may be shared or transferred with or to our affiliates, licensees and partners or otherwise disclosed as we deem necessary, in our sole discretion, to comply with any applicable law(s), regulation(s), legal process(es) or governmental request(s).

#### 2\. Log Files

We may use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer our website, track traffic patterns and gather demographic information for aggregate use. 

#### 3\. Third Parties

We may retain other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include data analysis firms, customer support specialists, webhosting companies, and fulfillment companies (i.e. companies that coordinate mailings). Such third parties may be provided with access to Personal Information needed to perform their functions. 

#### 4\. Links

This website may contain links to or from other websites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites. This Privacy Policy applies only to the information we collect on or through this website. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of other websites you link to from our website or otherwise visit.

#### 5\. Changes to Privacy Policy

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time without prior notice. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post the revised policy here. As we may make changes at any time, please periodically review the latest version of this Privacy Policy posted here. Please note that such changes will take effect immediately and what we do with information provided by you will be in accordance with the latest version of this Privacy Policy as posted here.

[](https://www.emaar.com/en/ "Emaar group")Copyright © Reel Entertainment LLC. All rights reserved.
